RG 062:043, Town of East Hartford
Connecticut State Library
Town of East Hartford records
1827-1977
Connecticut State Library
East Hartford (Conn.)
355 cubic feet
Administrative, poor relief, land, military, vital, school, election, tax, financial, boards and commissions, and fire district records for the town of East Hartford.
RG062_043
2009-014 (except where noted)
Historical Note
The town of East Hartford was incorporated in October 1783 and was taken from Hartford. Manchester separated from East Hartford in 1823.
Beginning in the late nineteenth century, residents began to form tax districts for fire protection, street lighting, sanitation, and other public works improvements. The East Hartford Fire District was granted a charter by the General Assembly in 1889 and organized in June, 1891. The Meadow Fire District existed before the turn of the twentieth century. The Hockanum Sewer District and Hockanum Lighting District were formed in 1915 and 1916 respectively. The Silver Lane Fire and Lighting District was founded in 1925. On June 10, 1929, voters of the town approved a new charter. All of the old districts were abolished and a Town Council would govern the municipality.1
Notes:
1Lee Paquette, Only More So: The History of East Hartford, 1783-1976 (East Hartford, Conn.: Raymond Library Company, 1976), 146, 205-206, 239.
Scope and Content
Series 1. Administrative Records, 1862-1967, contain a variety of material including various town papers dating from 1862 to 1870 such as abatements, meeting notices, petitions, reports, and town orders. There is also a Selectmen's minute book, 1926-1929.
Series 2. Poor Relief Records, 1926-1936, primarily cover the years of the Great Depression. Included are family assistance account books, 1926-1933; poor support ledgers, 1933-1936; and poor support books, 1928-1933.
Series 4. Military Records, circa 1861-1922, include a variety of Civil War papers such as: Changes in the Connecticut Volunteer Force in the Field; Committee for the Relief of Drafted Men; Payments to Connecticut volunteers; Enlistment expenses; military tax; and list of soldiers with families receiving support. Also present are military enrollments, 1902-1922 and a discharge book, 1923-1945.
Series 6. School Records, 1863-1911, include two volumes from the South School District: a secretary's minute book, 1839-1867 and a treasurer's account book, 1858-1911.
The bulk of Series 7. Election Records, 1837-1929, are lists of electors, or voters' lists, that cover town, state, and national elections from 1840 to 1929. Also included is a volume of electors admitted, 1876-1898, election returns, 1870-1920; and a list of women who registered to vote for school officer, 1893-1917.
Series 8. Tax Records, 1827-1945, contain a variety of records including individual tax lists, 1869-1929; old age assistance tax lists, 1935-1936; old age assistance tax cashier stubs, 1940-1941; personal tax additions, 1932, 1934; rate books, 1856-1865, 1923-1945; street books, 1894, 1903, 1912, 1921; and tax abstracts, 1836-1945. Tax abstracts beginning in 1836 include separate columns for name, number of polls, buildings, land, horses, cattle, sheep, money at interest, and luxury goods such as chaises and watches. Automobiles are mentioned starting in 1909. Tax abstracts from 1935 to 1945 cover real estate only.
Series 9. Financial Records, 1837-1946, contain a variety of record books such as account books, appropriation ledgers, cash journals, charity time books, check stub books, day books, general ledgers, municipal store cash books, orders, payroll, receipts and expenditures, selectmen's orders, and treasurer's payments. Also included are two Federal Emergency Relief Administration (FERA) project time books that list individuals who worked on various projects.
Series 10. Boards, Commissions, and Committees Records, 1929-1977, include administrative files for the American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1973-1977. The bulk of the series are minutes for the Claims Committee, 1931-1937; Board of Finance, 1929-1957 (original), 1961-1967 (photocopy); and Hockanum Cemetery Committee, 1933-1948. Also present are photocopies of minutes for the Insurance Committee, 1945-1968; Park Board, 1945-1968; Board of Police Commissioners, 1929-1945, 1956-1969; and Board of Welfare Commissioners, 1955-1960, 1965.
The bulk of Series 11. District Records, 1890-1932, pertains to the East Hartford Fire District. Included are administrative files, annual and special meeting minutes, Board of Commissioner minutes, financial records and tax records. Also represented are the Hockanum Lighting District, Hockanum Sewer District, Meadow Fire District, and Silver Lane Fire and Lighting District. There is a small amount of material that postdate the abolishment of the districts by the charter in 1929.
Related Material
RG 069:091 Percy S. Bryant Papers includes documents related to the East Hartford Fire District.
The following are found in the Classified Archives:
List of electors qualified to vote in electors' meeting, 1881 November 8 [CSL call number StLib Archives 974.62 Ea751]
Selectmen's reports & accounts, 1852-1868; papers on town poor, 1854-1870; land, legal & miscellaneous papers, 1854-1870 [CSL call number StLib Archives 974.62 Ea75s]
Town treasurer's book, 1784-1807. Last audit, 1808 January 1 [CSL call number 974.62 Ea75tr]
Index Terms
Alternate Creators:
East Hartford (Conn.). American Revolution Bicentennial Commission; East Hartford (Conn.). Board of Finance; East Hartford (Conn.). Fire District; East Hartford (Conn.). Hockanum Lighting District; East Hartford (Conn.). Hockanum Sewer District; East Hartford (Conn.). Meadow Fire District; East Hartford (Conn.). Silver Lane Fire and Lighting District
Subjects:
Taxation -- Connecticut -- East Hartford -- Registers; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- East Hartford -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- East Hartford -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- East Hartford -- Registers; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- East Hartford; Voting -- Connecticut -- East Hartford -- Statistics; Elections -- Connecticut -- East Hartford -- Statistics; Public welfare -- Connecticut -- East Hartford; Soldiers -- Connecticut -- East Hartford; School enrollment -- Connecticut -- East Hartford -- Statistics
Places:
East Hartford (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence; East Hartford (Conn.) -- Centennial celebrations, etc; East Hartford (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital
Restrictions on Access
Boxes 49 and 69 are restricted due to water damage. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Administrative Records, 1862-1967
  The records found in Box 1, Folders 1-6, were purchased from H.A. Armstrong, December 11, 1941.
  - Abatements, 1864-1870 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    See also: Abatement list, 1835-1882, in Record Book in Box 18.
  - Financial reports, 1863-1870 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting notices, 1870 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Petitions, 1864-1870, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1870, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Town orders, 1862-1870 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Field and Playground Association of East Hartford cash book, 1913-1922; 1 volume (Box 2)
  - Cemetery lot receipts, 1891-1915; 1 volume (Box 2)
  - Dog registers (Box 2)
    See also: Dog register, 1855-1871, in volume of electors admitted in Box 18.
    - 1878-1887, 1 volume (Box 2)
    - 1887-1896, 1 volume (Box 2)
    - 1896-1905, 1 volume (Box 2)
    - 1905-1908, 1 volume (Box 2)
    - 1910-1914, 1 volume (Box Item 3)
    - 1914-1916, 1 volume (Box 2)
    - 1917-1919, 1 volume (Box 2)
    - 1920-1921, 1 volume (Box 2)
    - 1922, 1 volume (Box 2)
  - Motor boats, 1915-1917; 1 notebook (Box 2)
  - Physicians, Registered, 1893-1967; 1 volume (Box 2)
  - Selectmen minute book, 1926-1929; 1 volume (Box 2)
  - Trade names, 1921-1953; 1 volume (Box 2)
  - Unidentified index, circa 1930-1931 (Box 2)
- Series 2. Poor Relief Records, 1926-1936
  - Family assistance account books (Box 6)
    - 1926-1931, 1 binder (Box 6)
    - 1931-1932, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1932-1933, 2 volumes (Box 6)
  - Poor support ledgers
    - 1933-1934, 1 post binder (Box Item 4)
    - 1934-1936, 1 post binder (Box Item 5)
  - Poor support books (Box 6)
    - 1929-1930, 1 notebook (Box 6)
    - 1931-1932, 1 notebook (Box 6)
    - 1932-1933, 1 notebook (Box 6)
    - 1933, 2 notebooks (Box 6)
    - Other towns, 1928-1931; 1 notebook (Box 6)
- Series 3. Land Records, undated
  - Town deeds and historical notes concerning land and roads, etc.; From town records, etc., 1640-1879, undated (Box 7)
- Series 4. Military Records, circa 1861-1922
  The records found in Box 1, Folders 7-13, were purchased from H.A. Armstrong, December 11, 1941.
  - Changes in the Connecticut Volunteer Force in the Field, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Committee for the Relief of Drafted Men, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut volunteers, Payments to, circa 1861-1865 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Enlistment expenses, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - List of men with ages, circa 1864-1865 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Military tax, circa 1861-1865 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Soldiers with families receiving support, 1862-1863, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Military enrollments (Box 7)
    - 1902-1914, 1 volume (Box 7)
    - 1914-1919, 1 volume (Box 7)
    - 1919-1922, 1 volume (Box 7)
  - Military registrations, 1917; 1 volume (Box 7)
  - Soldiers and sailors discharges, 1923-1945; 1 volume (Box 7)
- Series 5. Vital Records, 1923-1931
  - Sexton returns, 1923-1931; 1 volume (Box 7)
    Contents: Center Cemetery; St. Mary's Cemetery; Hockanum Cemetery.
- Series 6. School Records, 1863-1911
  - School visitors, 1863, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Purchased from H.A. Armstrong, December 11, 1941.
  - Second North District school register, 1873-1874 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Second South School District secretary's minutes, 1839 September 23 - 1867 September 18; 1 volume (Box 7)
  - South School District treasurer's account book, 1858-1911; 1 volume (Box 7)
- Series 7. Election Records, 1837-1929
  - Electors, Lists of
    - State, 1840 April; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - National, 1840 November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, 1841 April; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, 1842 April; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - National, 1844 November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, 1845 April; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, 1846 April; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, amendment to the constitution, town, 1847 April, October, November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, town, 1848 April, November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - National, 1848 November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, 1849 April; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, amendment to the constitution, town, 1850 April; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, town, 1851 April, November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, town, 1852 April, November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - National, 1852 November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, 1854 April; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, 1855 April; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, town, 1856 April, November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, town, 1857 April, November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, town, 1858 April, November; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - State, 1859 April; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - National, 1860 National; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - National, corrected list, 1860 November; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - 1861 April, 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Corrected list, 1861 April; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - List for correction, 1862 April; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Corrected list, 1862 April; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Corrected list, 1863 April; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - National, 1864 November; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Corrected list, 1866 April; 1 volume (Box 10)
    - 1866 November, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - Corrected list, town, 1867 April, November; 1 volume (Box 10)
    - Corrected list, town, 1868 April, October; 1 volume (Box 10)
    - 1868 November, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - 1869 April, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - 1870 April, October, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - 1871 April, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - 1872 April, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - 1872 November, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - 1873 April, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - 1874 April, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - 1875 April, October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1876 April, October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1876 November, 1877 September, October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1877 November, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1878 November, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1879 October, November, 1880 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1880 November, 1881 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1881 November, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1882 November, 1883 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1883 November, 1884 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1884 November, 1885 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1885 November, 1886 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1886 November, 1887 May, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1887 October, 1888 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1888 November, 1889 October, 1890 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1890 November, 1891 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1892 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1892 November, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1892 November, 1893 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1894 October, 1 volume (Box 11)
    - 1894 November, 1895 October, 1 volume (Box 12)
    - 1896 October, 1 volume (Box 12)
    - National, 1896 November; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Town, 1897 October; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Town, 1898 October; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - State, 1898 November; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Town, 1899 October; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Town, 1900 October; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - State, National, 1900 November; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Town, 1901 October; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Delegate to constitutional convention, 1901 November; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Proposed constitutional convention, 1902 June; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Town, 1902 October; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - State, 1902 November; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - 1903 October, 1 volume (Box 13)
    - Town, 1904 October; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - State, 1904 November; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - Town, 1905 October; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - State, 1906 November; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - Town, 1907 October; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - Town, 1908 October; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - State, 1908 November; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - Town, 1909 October; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - Town, 1910 October; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - State, 1910 November; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - School question, 1911 June; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Town, 1911 October; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Town, 1912 October; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - State, 1912 November; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Town, 1913 October; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Town, 1914 October; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - State, 1914 November; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Town, 1915 October; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Town, 1916 October; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - National, 1916 November; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Town, 1917 October; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Town, 1918 October; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - State, 1918 November; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Town, 1919 October; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Town, 1920 October; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - National, state, A-J, 1920 November; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - National, state, K-Z, 1920 November; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Town, 1921 October; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Town, A-J, 1922 October; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Town, K-Z, 1922 October; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - State, A-J, 1922 November; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - State, K-Z, 1922 November; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Town, A-J, 1923 October; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Town, K-Z, 1923 October; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Town, A-J, 1924 October (Box 16)
    - Town, K-Z, 1924 October; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - National, A-J, 1924 November; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - National, K-Z, 1924 November; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - Senate, A-J, 1924 December; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - Senate, K-Z, 1924 December; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - A-J, 1925 October; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - K-Z, 1925 October; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - A-J, 1926 October; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - K-Z, 1926 October; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - Town, A-J, 1927 October; 1 volume (Box 17)
    - Town, K-Z, 1927 October; 1 volume (Box 17)
    - Town, 1928 October; 1 volume (Box 17)
    - National, 1928 November; 1 volume (Box 17)
    - Special election, 1929 June; 1 volume (Box 17)
  - Electors admitted, 1876-1898; 1 volume (Box 18)
    Also includes: Dog register, 1855-1871; Liquor license applications, 1872-1919.
  - Record book, 1835-1922; 1 volume (Box 18)
    Contents: Lists of electors, 1837-1844, 1873; Women who registered to vote for school officer, 1893-1917; Report of the treasurer, 1837-1858; Abatement list, 1835-1882.
  - Returns to Comptroller and Secretary of State, Duplicates of election and tax (Box 18)
    - 1827-1901, 1 volume (Box 18)
      Contents: Election returns, 1870-1901; Tax returns, 1827-1900
    - 1902-1922, 1 volume (Box 18)
      Contents: Election returns, 1902-1920; Tax returns, 1901-1922
  - Voter lists, 1880-1887; 5 notebooks (Box 18)
- Series 8. Tax Records, 1827-1945
  - Apt. tax list, 1933-1934 (Box 49)
    Box 49 restricted due to water damage.
  - Assessment book, 1933-1943; 1 post binder (Box Item 25)
  - Assessors stockholders lists, 1888-1990 (Box 19)
  - Individual tax lists, 1869-1929; 428 volumes + 7 bundles + 2 boxes; T003120
    Bundles for 1876, 1877, 1878 have been separated due to water damage.
    Note accession number for this item.
  - Journal, undated; 1 volume (Box 20)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 20)
  - Old age assistance tax list (Box 20)
    - 1935, 1 post binder (Box 20)
    - 1936, 1 post binder (Box 20)
  - Old age assistance tax cashier stubs, 1940-1941 (Box 21-22)
  - Personal tax additions
    - A-K, 1932; 1 binder (Box 23)
    - L-Z, 1932; 1 binder (Box 23)
    - A-H, 1934; 1 binder (Box 23)
    - K-Z, 1934; 1 binder (Box 23)
  - Rate books, 1856-1865, 1923-1945
    Rate books 1929-1945 are not assigned item numbers. Researchers should indicate year when requesting these.
    - 1856, 2 notebooks (Box 26)
    - 1857, 1 notebook (Box 26)
    - 1858, 1 notebook (Box 26)
    - 1859, 1 notebook (Box 26)
    - 1860, 1 notebook (Box 26)
    - 1861, 1 notebook (Box 26)
    - 1862, 1 notebook (Box 26)
    - 1863, 1 notebook (Box 26)
    - 1865, 1 notebook (Box 26)
    - 1923, 1 post binder (Box Item 27)
    - 1924, 1 post binder (Box Item 28)
    - 1925, 1 post binder (Box Item 29)
    - 1926, 1 post binder (Box Item 30)
    - 1927, 1 post binder (Box Item 31)
    - 1928, 1 post binder (Box Item 32)
    - 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939, 1940, 1941, 1942, 1943, 1944, 1945, 17 post binders
  - Street books
    - 1894, 1 volume (Box 24)
    - 1903, 1 volume (Box 24)
    - 1912, 1 volume (Box 24)
    - 1921, 1 volume (Box 24)
  - Tax abstracts
    Tax abstracts 1914-1945 are not assigned item numbers. Researchers should indicate year when requesting these.
    - 1836, 1837, 1838, 1839, 1840, 1841, 1842, 1843, 1844, 9 volumes (Box 33)
    - 1845, 1846, 1847, 1848, 1849, 1850, 6 volumes (Box 34)
    - 1851, 1852, 1853, 1854, 1855, 5 volumes (Box 35)
    - 1856, 1857, 1858, 1859, 1860, 5 volumes (Box 36)
    - 1861, 1862, 1863-1864, 1865, 4 volumes (Box 37)
    - 1866, 1867, 1868, 1869, 1870, 1871, 6 volumes (Box 38)
    - 1872, 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876, 5 volumes (Box 39)
    - 1877, 1878, 1879, 1880, 1881, 5 volumes (Box 40)
    - 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886, 5 volumes (Box 41)
    - 1887, 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891, 5 volumes (Box 42)
    - 1892, 1893, 1894, 1895, 4 volumes (Box 43)
    - 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899, 4 volumes (Box 44)
    - 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903, 4 volumes (Box 45)
    - 1904, 1905, 1906, 1907, 4 volumes (Box 46)
    - 1908, 1909, 1910, 3 volumes (Box 47)
    - 1911, 1912, 1913, 3 volumes (Box 48)
    - 1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939, 1940, 1941, 1942, 1943, 1944, 1945, 32 volumes
  - Tax collector books
    - 1875, 1 volume (Box 20)
    - 1894, 1 volume (Box 20)
    - 1871, 1872, 1877, 1878, 1887, 1889, 1895, 1901, 1906, 9 items (Box 49)
  - Tax returns to the Comptroller, Duplicates of, 1827-1922 (Box 18)
    These records are in two volumes with election returns to the Secretary of the State. Because of this they are also reference in Series 7, Election Records.
- Series 9. Financial Records, 1837-1946
  - Account book, 1907-1910; 1 volume (Box 69)
    Box 69 is restricted due to water damage.
  - Appropriation ledgers
    - FY 1930-1931, 1931-1932, 1932-1933, 1 post binder (Box Item 50)
    - FY 1933-1934, 1934-1935, 1 post binder (Box Item 51)
    - FY 1935-1936, 1936-1937, 1 post binder (Box Item 52)
    - FY 1937-1938, 1938-1939, 1 post binder (Box Item 53)
    - FY 1938-1940, 1 post binder (Box Item 54)
      Also includes Receipts, 1938-1941.
    - FY 1939-1940, 1940-1941, 1 post binder (Box Item 55)
    - FY 1941-1942, 1 post binder (Box Item 56)
    - FY 1942-1943, 1 post binder (Box Item 57)
    - FY 1943-1944, 1944-1945, 1 post binder (Box Item 58)
    - FY 1945-1946, 1 post binder (Box Item 59)
  - Appropriations and expenditures, 1929-1930; 1 volume (Box 69)
  - Bonds, Record of registered, 1926-1928; 1 volume (Box 60)
  - Cash book, 1925-1928; 1 volume (Box 60)
  - Cash deposits, 1925-1927; 1 volume (Box 60)
  - Cash journals (Box 60)
    - 1930, 1 volume (Box 60)
    - 1930-1933, 1 volume (Box 60)
    - 1934-1937, 1 volume (Box 60)
    - 1937, 1 volume (Box 60)
  - Center Cemetery trust funds, 1921-1935; 1 volume (Box 60)
  - Charity time books (Box 61)
    - Park Dept., 1932-1933 (Box 61)
    - Street Dept., 1932-1933 (Box 61)
    - Water Dept., 1933 (Box 61)
  - Check stub books (Box 61)
    - 1870-1875, 1 unbound item (Box 68)
    - 1875-1880, 1 unbound item (Box 68)
    - 1880-1886, 1 volume (Box 69)
    - 1886-1889, 1 volume (Box 69)
    - 1891-1893, 1 volume (Box 61)
    - 1924-1927, 1 volume (Box 61)
    - 1926, 1 volume (Box 61)
    - 1926-1927, 1 volume (Box 61)
    - 1929, 1 volume (Box 61)
    - 1931-1941, 1 volume (Box 61)
    - 1931-1941, 1 volume (Box 61)
    - Teachers salaries, circa 1900; 1 volume (Box 69)
    - Town employees, 1932; 1 volume (Box 61)
    - Water account, 1929-1930; 1 volume (Box 61)
    - Water account, 1930-1940; 1 volume (Box 61)
    - Water account, 1932-1940; 1 volume (Box 61)
  - Corporation tax, 1925-1934, 1937 (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
    Consists of lists of stock holders.
  - Daybook (payments), 1897-1907; 1 volume (Box 69)
  - Daybook, 1907-1919; 1 volume (Box Item 72)
  - Daybook, 1917-1927; 1 volume (Box Item 71)
  - Earnings records, 1941-1943 (Box 62)
  - Education (Board of) accounts and payroll, 1940 October - 1943 September (Box 67, Folder 5-6)
  - Expenditures for schools, Distribution of, 1924-1928; 1 unbound item (Box 68)
  - Federal Emergency Relief Administration (FERA) (Box 63)
    - Compensation day book, 1934-1935; 1 volume (Box 63)
    - Fund control register, 1935; 1 volume (Box 63)
    - Time book projects (Box 63)
      - 1934-1935, 1 volume (Box 63)
      - 1934-1935, 1 volume (Box 63)
  - General journal, 1931-1935; 1 volume (Box Item 73)
  - General ledgers (Box 64)
    - 1929-1930, 1 volume (Box 64)
    - 1931-1935, 1 post binder (Box 64)
    - 1932-1935, 1 post binder (Box 64)
    - 1944-1945, 1 post binder (Box 64)
  - Highway work payments book, 1887-1916; 1 volume (Box Item 74)
  - Indexing order book, 1883; 1 volume (Box 69)
  - Journal, 1930-1935, 1937 (Box 65)
  - Municipal store books (Box 65)
    - 1934-1935 August, 1 volume (Box 65)
    - 1935 August - 1937, 1 volume (Box 65)
  - Notes payment book, Town, 1907-1918; 1 volume (Box 66)
  - Order book, Town (Daybook), 1855-1876; 1 volume (Box 66)
  - Orders, Town, 1921-1929; 1 volume (Box 69)
  - Orders, Treasurer payments on town, 1924-1927; 1 unbound item (Box 68)
  - Payroll books (Box 65)
    - 1931-1933, 1 volume (Box 65)
    - 1933-1935, 1 volume (Box 65)